{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Baseboard \u0026 Wall Heater Installation Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40875/":{"taskOID":40875,"originalTaskOID":40875,"setID":761,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":3083,"questionDisplayText":"Choose electric wall heat type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of electric wall heating would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":953,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Baseboard style","answerDisplayText":"Baseboard style","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6740,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall fan unit","answerDisplayText":"Wall fan unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6946,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of the area the electric wall heating system will cover?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10185,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10186,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10187,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6947,"questionDisplayText":"Number of rooms to be heated","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms will require electric wall heating?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10189,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11 - 15","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10192,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10193,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":3083,"questionDisplayText":"Choose electric wall heat type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of electric wall heating would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":953,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Baseboard style","answerDisplayText":"Baseboard style","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6740,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall fan unit","answerDisplayText":"Wall fan unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":953,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Baseboard style","answerDisplayText":"Baseboard style","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6740,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall fan unit","answerDisplayText":"Wall fan unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6946,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of the area the electric wall heating system will cover?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10185,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10186,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10187,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10185,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10186,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10187,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6947,"questionDisplayText":"Number of rooms to be heated","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms will require electric wall heating?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10189,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11 - 15","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10192,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10193,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10189,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11 - 15","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10192,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10193,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40875/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40875,"taskName":"Electrical Baseboard or Wall Heater - Install","taskDescription":"Install an Electrical Baseboard or Wall Heater","xmTaskDescriptor":"Baseboard \u0026 Wall Heater Installation Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":70,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Heater Electrical systems condition ac","textMessagingName":"Install Elec Heater","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically used in additions, vacation homes where gas isn't available or to augment heat pumps \u0026 wood stoves. Most common version is a long metal box mounted an inch or two off the floor along one wall in a room.","rolloverShortDesc":"Not for hot water radiators.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install an Electrical Baseboard or Wall Heater.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Wall Heater Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Electric Baseboard Heater Install","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Electric Baseboard or Wall Heater Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Electrical Baseboard or Wall Heater - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Wall Heating Project","urlName":"Electrical-Baseboard-or-Wall-Heater-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Wall \u0026 Baseboard Heater Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Heat,Electrical, HVAC,Wall, radiator,furnace,floor, boiler, lamp,heat,vents, ducts,Water, baseboard","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":761,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isCookielessUser":true}